So today, whoever among us three siblings
collects the most coins during the civilized journey will
get a chance to eat his/her favorite food.
[screaming voice] Yes, but
before that I have to convince my sisters
because Hitler Didi and I had a
fight that was more dangerous than just a hand-to-hand fight.
Yes, so to please them I
perform their aarti with a candle.
After which they become about 50% happy and
they get the remaining 50% happiness like this.
Yes, then I will bring my 24 carat gold
phone.  And
after downloading the civilized travel game,
Hitler Didi comes first for running.
[screaming]
Congratulations, he collected all 31 coins.
Then it was my turn and
after running with full enthusiasm, I got 249 coins in my pocket
and then it was Dolo's turn
who broke my world record as soon as he came
and while running, he also
made a world record of 712 coins by flying.  Yes,
then dancing on his tunes, I
take both of them to the restaurant
and their order is
Lassi with Paneer Noodles.  Well, tell us by commenting how many coins you have collected in your civilized journey
and also subscribe to know.